question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "A slug's blood is green.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential "
                    "motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    }
]
